Pretty clear. Heh.
(Bernadette:)Do I look like I feel better?
(Howard:)I mean, it's not, like, HD quality.
Listen, you're gonna talk to your mother
and you're gonna fix this.
(Bernadette:)Or that thing I said I was gonna do to you
when you got home...
(Bernadette:)...you can do to yourself.
(Dimitri:)Like he's been doing since he got here.
(Amy:)Sheldon, this place is so romantic.
Aw... I'm glad you like it. Raj picked it out.
(Amy:)When you see him,
tell him I say thank you.
(Sheldon:)Tell him yourself.
(Raj:)Yoo-hoo! Over here.
(Amy:)I don't understand. What's he doing here?
- I invited him.
- On our date?
(Amy:)Sheldon, that's not okay.
Oh. Yes, it is. There's a loophole
in the relationship agreement.